Preliminary Guide to the Mount Vernon Seminary and College Nebraska Avenue Campus collection, 1917-1942 MVC0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera and documents, 1925-1941; Series 3; 2.5 Linear Feet
  - "Guard's Guide to Washington D.C.", 1926-1927; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets, 1921-1930; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Pamphlets and programs, 1932-1935; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Papers, correspondence, photocopies of pictures of Mount Vernon campus, Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Programs, Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1904-1941; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - MVC event programs, 1927-1929; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Report on the MVS Society and its Chapters, 1938; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Senior Class Song, Photos, Correspondence, 1930-1970; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Twelfth Annual Meeting of MVS Council, 1942; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Uniform guidelines, Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth Somers Chapel committee, Recording Secretary's book, 1920-1924; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth Somers Chapel Fund, 1919-1924; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth Somers Chapel papers, correspondence, chimes pamphlet, 1924-1932; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Centenary Celebration newspaper clippings, 1937; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Centenary Celebration notes and programs, 1937; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Alumni list attending Elizabeth Somers Centenary, 1937; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Centenary Celebration endowment campaign, 1936-1937; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Anne Seymour Ames, correspondence and papers, 1940-1956; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and papers concerning Ames memorial service, 1959; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - "Golden Jubilee March" score, 1925; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Golden Jubilee calendar, 1925; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "The Cloister Columns" newspaper, 1933-1936; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Somers Chapel, Ames Bell, 1925; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Somers Chapel organ, 1925-1926; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "A Happy New Year" Chapel Prayer by Anne Seymour Ames, 1928; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Artifacts, Series 4; 2 Linear Feet
  This series contains plaques, medals, textiles, and dormitory room numbers from the Nebraska Avenue campus. Items date from 1923 to 1937.
  - Nebraska Avenue plaque, 1924; Series 4 (Box 20)
  - Alice Trippett, Field House plaque, Series 4 (Box 21)
  - "Class of" plaque, Series 4 (Box 22)
  - 2 small plaques for Centenary Celebration, 1937; Series 4 (Box 23, Item 1)
  - Medal for distinguished service to the alma mater, 1937; Series 4 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Linen towels made from MVS uniforms, from Virginia More Roediger Johnson, 1923-1925; Series 4 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - Winter wool uniform chevron, Series 4 (Box 23, Item 4)
  - Small plaque, Series 4 (Box 23, Item 5)
  - Metal dorm room numbers, Series 4 (Box 23, Item 6)
  - Anne Seymour Ames, bell-shaped "Her Book of Remembrance", 1925; Series 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)